Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Disaster Begins
Episode 3
This is truly a disaster
I wonder how Wolffy is doing now
Why is this so dark?
Weslie you
My head hurts so much
Have I already
where am i
Who put such a sloppy rag doll here?
Grandpa, he woke up
and scolded me when he woke up
What’s going on? The rag doll is talking.
Why are they all wool toys?
Where is this?
There are woolen dolls everywhere
So dirty
what happened to my hands
What’s going on?
How come I turned into a stuffed toy?
Is this a dream? Wake up.
He broke our mirror
Pay up immediately.
Everyone, calm down. He must have broken his head.
So it’s a little abnormal
Please be tolerant, everyone.
This must be a dream
Wake up quickly, wake up
Okay, then keep an eye on him and don’t let him run around.
Okay, okay
It hurts so much. It seems like I’m not dreaming.
Was it that time?
So it’s all because of that shadow man
By the way, Weslie should be in this world too
I need to find Weslie quickly
What’s wrong with me
You must be starving
Can rag dolls be hungry too?
Of course
No matter what, meals should always come first.
Your food is this cotton?
I can actually eat it and it tastes good
Which one looks more delicious?
So unpalatable
Of course it’s a stool
Only Bulala processed into food is delicious
Really? Where can I eat processed Bulala?
Please enjoy your meal.
Why are you so stingy and give me so little?
This is called exquisiteness
I’ll give you the rest of the Bulala. Eat it quickly.
This meal is so stressful
So delicious
Soft and slippery
I didn’t expect that a small Bulala could make such delicious food
Of course in Bulala City
In addition to processing Bulala into food, people
can make them into anything
Can make a house
gardening
This is really a magical place
Thank you for your hospitality. I’m going to find my friend Weslie.
Are you looking for Weslie? Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
do you know weslie
Weslie
This is the microphone
dad dad dad
Okay, I got it
He said he was at the palace
Really? Where is the palace?
right there
Go in quickly
I’m really not a Bulala
My name is Weslie from Green Green Grassland
So your name is Weslie
What a nice name
You finally believe it
Go in
Don’t look at it. This is just a place to store Bulala.
what do you want to do
Of course we want to feel the touch of you rare Bulala
I’ve looked through the books and there’s no record of this kind of Bulala.
The Bulala smells really good. Just smelling it makes you feel like you will live longer for several years.
It’s so comfortable
You should be in the storage room for this rare Bulala
I originally thought the fire burn Bulala or
thunder and lightning Bulala are already very rare.
But it’s nothing compared to this Bulala
Isn’t it a pity to offer such a rare Bulala?
How about we take it home and collect it?
Looking at your potential, of course we will dedicate him to Master Quan.
Maybe if Master Quan is happy, we can even become generals.
He wanted to be a general so he offered me up. His wish came true.
But what about you?
Are you really happy if you become a general?
me me me
Are you trying to sow discord? You’re too naïve.
Do you think the relationship between us brothers for more than 20 years is just paper?
Stay here honestly and we will report to Master Quan now.
Wait I’m really not a Bulala
let me go
I didn’t expect these two people to be incompetent.
I have to find a way to escape quickly.
What you said makes sense
I secretly cut a little Bulala
Don’t shout
As expected, my simple brother
How can you do big things if you can’t resist this little temptation?
You only want what you want, but you don’t care what I want
I don’t want to be a general
I just want to enjoy life
Be a happy Bulala
If I hadn’t taken you with me all these years and been held back by you,
I have become a general long ago
You really are a hopeless case—like trying to plaster mud onto a wall.
You’re calling me a wall? I think you’re the one who’s a wall.
You dare talk back? Looks like you’re overdue for a lesson.
I’ve hated you for ages; I’ve always had to wear your hand-me-downs.
I can’t stand you either—a new game console,
you broke it in just two days.
Nephew, it’s time to take medicine
drink slowly
Uncle, is there really no other way?
Apart from paying tribute to Bulala to appease the monster, there is currently no better way.
What about Golden Bulala?
If we find the legendary Golden Bulala
Can we defeat the monster?
That’s fake. There is no Golden Bulala in the world.
But
Didn’t my father become the king just because he found the Golden Bulala?
If he really had the Golden Bulala, he wouldn’t have been defeated by the monster.
Are we going to keep going like this?
If you’re not feeling well these days, don’t worry about it anymore.
You should have a good rest. I will go out and be busy first.
Father
Do you have any other ideas?
Will something happen to him?
Should I save him?
Weslie
Let me see if you are hurt. Where does it hurt?
Why have you turned into a stuffed doll?
What are you doing Weslie
My name is Weslie but I don’t know you
Will you lose your memory when you become Bulala?
The Bulala you are looking for looks like me and was captured by soldiers and taken to the palace.
What? I go to save him.
Wait
The palace is very well guarded
I can enter the gate of Goats’ Village. What does it mean if it’s just the gate of the palace?
No one is allowed to enter the important area of the palace.
It’s indeed a bit difficult, but it can’t stop me King Wolffy
Do you want to continue after failing so many times?
Of course because he is my friend
Friend?
Wait a moment
It’s over. Where is the water? Put out the fire quickly.
How do you guard the warehouse?
This is the hard work of the residents for a week.
How can you afford them?
who did this
It was that Bulala named Weslie who did it
He provoked the two of us to secretly untie the rope and run away.
He also set fire to the warehouse
If you continue to let him go on like this
Maybe even our entire palace was destroyed by him
What
Someone come and catch him
yes
To be continued